DIWASH SAPKOTA

Digital Marketing Specialist

https://diwashsapkota.github.io



+977 9861640372

☐ diwashsapkota2080@gmail.com

PROFILE INFO

As a seasoned Digital Marketing & Website Specialist, I excel in enhancing the online presence of faith-based organizations and translating complex ideas into clear, effective language. With my rich background in research and leadership roles in ICT, I bring a unique blend of skills to any team, ready to communicate compelling messages and reach wider audiences.

EXPERIENCE

February, 2023 - Present

Joseph's Ministry, LLC | Oklahoma, USA (Remote)

Digital Marketing Specialist

- Creating and posting relevant content regularly across various social media platforms.
- Operating regular email campaigns.
- Handling the organization's business profile on Google.

March, 2019 - Present

Word and Life Church | Pennsylvania, USA (Remote)

Website/Digital Marketing Specialist

- Regularly updating and maintaining the church's website.
- Creating and editing visual content for social media platforms such as Facebook, Instagram, and YouTube.
- Operating regular email campaigns and doing Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to increase the church's online visibility.

December, 2017 - Present

Freelancing

Books, Articles Translator, Editor and Proofreader

- Translated books and sermons from English to Nepali and vice-versa.
- Editing and proofreading translated content to ensure accuracy and readability.
- Successfully translated and published three faith-based books so far.

April, 2023 - September, 2024

Numeric Mind Nepal Pvt. Ltd. | Kathmandu, Nepal

Data Analyst

- Conducted data cleaning, validation, and quality checks on clinical trial
- Generated CDISC-compliant datasets for regulatory submissions.
- Created macros to automate repetitive tasks and improve efficiency.
- Created summary tables, and listings for clinical study reports.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2022 | St. Xavier's College

BSc. Computer Science & Information Technology

Completed Undergraduate with several case studies, research projects, exceptional academic performance & was also honored with the student of the batch award.

2014 - 2016 | NIST Patan

High School

Completed high school with distinction, winning several accolades in the process.

SKILLS

- Digital Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Content Writing
- Website Management
- Editing & Proofreading
- **Book Translation**
- Research
- Leadership

REFERENCE

Meagan Pinkney

Founder/CEO

Joseph's Ministry, LLC

Email: meagan@josephsministryllc.com